[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question" : "Which technology is used for communication between devices over short distances?",
        "options": [
            "Bluetooth",
            "Ethernet",
            "IPhone",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "Bluetooth"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question" : "What does the term phishing mean in IT?",
        "options": [
            "Sending spam emails",
            "Creating strong passwords",
            "Attempting to steal sensitive information",
            "Catching a salmon down by the lake"
        ],
        "answer": "Attempting to steal sensitive information"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question" : "Which software is commonly used for creating spreadsheets?",
        "options": [
            "Powerpoint",
            "Excel",
            "Photoshop",
            "Word"
        ],
        "answer": "Excel"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question" : "Which type of file format is commonly used for images?",
        "options": [
            "JPG",
            "DOC",
            "MP3",
            "PDF"
        ],
        "answer": "JPG"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question" : "What is an example of an Operating System? (OS)",
        "options": [
            "Photoshop",
            "Microsoft Office",
            "Google Chrome",
            "Linux"
        ],
        "answer": "Linux"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question" : "Which answer is a programming language?",
        "options": [
            "Excel",
            "Slither",
            "Python",
            "Server"
        ],
        "answer": "Python"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question" : "Who is known for creating and adopting personal home computers?",
        "options": [
            "Steve Jobs",
            "Tom Brady",
            "Kanye West",
            "Both B and C"
        ],
        "answer": "Steve Jobs"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question" : "What does A.I. stand for?",
        "options": [
            "Art of Intel",
            "Applicable Interface",
            "Artificial Intelligence",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "Artificial Intelligence"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question" : "What city in the United States is known for it's IT community?",
        "options": [
            "Chicago",
            "Washington DC",
            "San Fransisco",
            "None of the above."
        ],
        "answer": "San Fransisco"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question" : "Are you interested in a career in IT?",
        "options": [
            "No",
            "Yes",
            "Maybe",
            "Never in a million years!"
        ],
        "answer": "Yes"
    }
]